Anthony Tanner

 $\begin{array}{l} \verb|anthony.tanner120gmail.com|\\ 07449868688 \end{array}$

Skills

- Teamwork: working with a number of people on large scale projects.
- Communication: leading technical discussions on resolving roadblocks within a project.
- Agile project management: daily and weekly meetings with my team to ensure progress on a timeline is maintained.
- Analytical thinking: debugging of obscure errors requiring breaking down and eliminating of potential causes over a large range of components.

Technical Skills

- Linux Operating Systems
- Embedded Systems
- Use of build systems inc. Yocto (for kernel building) and CMake (compiling large-scale C++ applications)
- Git and continuous integration environments
- Bash Scripting
- Web Technologies

Programming Languages

- C/C++
- Java
- Haskell
- Python
- C#
- JavaScript

Personal Statement

I am a reliable, hard-working, conscientious individual. I can work in a team or independently. Following my placement, I have experience working with embedded systems and learning new platforms quickly. I am confident tackling new challenges and technologies I have never seen before. I look forward to working in an exciting environment on interesting, new projects.

Experience

Intel (July 2021 - August 2022)

Video & Vision FPGA Software Engineer

Responsibilities:

- Expanding functionality of toolkits for providing UIs to video processing projects.
- Designing specialized operating systems for projects, enabling and disabling features using the Yocto build system.
- Debugging kernel drivers, software and hardware read/write transactions.
- Creating a new automation process for creating release packages for multiple projects.
- Ensuring software legal compliance on systems releases.
- Collaborating with multiple teams of different disciplines to integrate different platforms.

Jefferies Solicitors Limited (April 2020 - May 2020)

Administrative Assistant

I worked managing post for the solicitors, ensuring letters were correctly identified and assigned.

Boots (June 2019 - September 2019)

Customer Advisor

As a part of Boots, I worked within the store to deal with customer needs and organising stock both in the store and the stock room.

Education

University of Birmingham (2019-)

B.Sc. Computer Science with an Industrial Year

Expected 1st Class with Honours

Key completed modules:

- Artificial Intelligence 2:77%
- Security and Networks : 82%
- Systems Programming in C/C++:92%
- Functional Programming: 100%
- Team Project: 78%

Final year modules:

- \bullet Security of Real-World Systems
- Advanced Networking
- Computer Vision and Imaging
- Intelligent Interactive Systems
- Computer Science Project

St Ambrose College (2012-2019)

A-Levels

Mathematics (A*), Computer Science (A), Chemistry (A)

Interests

I enjoy all sports and played rugby union as well as league at school, university and club. I took part in tours to Ireland and to Australia. I keep in shape by going to the gym, running and bike riding. I am currently in the process of completing my Duke of Edinburgh gold course. I also enjoy cooking and gardening, volunteering for the conservation group which works on projects to grow a vegetable garden and maintain habitats around the Midlands.